朗尼  七年前的今天
Seven years ago today, Lonnie.
就今天
Today.
整整七年
Seven years!
否则他现在都该15岁了
He would have been 15!
但是你谋杀了那个孩子
But you murdered that boy.
我要申请遏制令
I'm getting a restraining order!
放心  你迟早会需要的
I'm gonna give you a reason
给你和你的变态儿子用
to need one one day-- you and your sick-ass son!
天哪  你现在都跟踪我们了吗
Oh, for God's sake. You're following us now?
玩的开心吗  朗尼
You having fun, Lonnie? Huh?
人生真不错啊对不对
Life's good, isn't it?
你离我们的距离不能小于30米的
You're not supposed to be within 100 feet of my family.
不要碰我
Don't touch me.
不不不  你需要去...
No, no, no. You need to get--
你们都知道他的所作所为
You all know what he did.
真让我恶心
You make me sick.
那哥们儿就穿过院子
And so this brother comes across the yard.
他应该是毒品搞多了还是什么
He's all skeezed out on crystal or something.
然后他说  "鸡肉派"
And he says, he says, "Chicken pot pie."
好像我知道那是什么东西似的
Like I'm supposed to know what that is, right?
然后我手下的的人看着他
So my boy looks at him,
指着街道后面跟他说
points back at the block and he says,
"那边"
"That way."
那家伙想找什么不重要
Did not matter what this cat was on.
他只是想强调他是从英国来的
He just doubles back to where he came from lickety-split,
知道我的意思吗
you know what I'm saying?
J  听我说  我有消息跟你说
Hey, J, listen, I got some news. Um...
我动用了点关系  把你送进芝加哥交管局了
I had to pull some strings, but I got you in at the CTA.
那里...
That's where--
城里的人不是都把废物亲戚往那里送吗
That's where city workers send their loser relatives.
那是一份工作
It's a job.
而且会帮你重新开始的
And it'll help you get back on your feet.
你现在说话越来越像他了你知道吗
You know you sound more and more like him every day, right?
周一开始去上班
You start Monday.
好的  老爸  没问题
Okay, pop, sure.
失陪  我去接个电话
Excuse me, I gotta take this.
喂
Hello?
世事真是无常啊  对吧
Strange how things worked out, huh?
为什么
How's that?
我们收养你的时候  你是有问题的人
When we took you in, you were the problem.
可现在你是大家眼中的好孩子
And now you're the golden girl,
而我是回头的浪子
and I'm the prodigal son.
事已至此  贾斯汀
Well, here we are, Justin.
现在你有改过自新的机会
And now you have a second chance,
所以不要浪费掉了
so don't piss on it.
我们得走了
We gotta roll.
抱歉  孩子
I'm sorry, kid.
房子是迪恩·马斯特斯的
House belongs to a Dean Masters.
他的档案被着重标记通知情报组了
His file was red-flagged to notify intelligence,
这人肯定在我进警署之前就出名了
but he must have been before my time.
对啊  是他
Oh, yeah, him.
去年艺术学院的那个抢劫犯
That robbery at the art institute last year.
他就是个买卖贼赃的人
We liked him as the fence.
邻居听到有女人喊叫
The neighbors heard a woman scream.
我们敲门他说手里有枪  让我们离远点
We knocked, he yelled out that he had a gun and to leave him alone.
马斯特斯  我是芝加哥警署的博伊特警长
Masters, this is Sergeant Voight with the Chicago Police.
快开门  我们好好解决问题
Open up, make this easy on all of us.
-他会杀我的  -上吧
- He's gonna kill me! - Take it.
-放下枪  -我说过我会杀了她的
- Drop it! - I told 'em I would kill her!
放下枪  马斯特斯
Drop it, Masters!
-我们是来帮忙的  -放开她
- We're here to help. - Let her go.
我们只是想好好玩玩
All we're trying to do is have a good time.
对不对啊
Isn't that right, huh?
放下武器  举起手来
Drop your weapon! Hands in the air!
马上
Do it now!
不要紧张  大家都深呼吸
Easy, easy. Everybody take a breath.
她陷害我  她想害死我
She set me up. She's trying to get me killed.
好  你说得对  我们会好好处理的
Fine, you're right. We can handle that.
我知道情报  我知道有笔交易的情报
I got info. I got info on a deal that's going down,
所以她才陷害我的
and that's why she's setting me up.
我不知道  不知道他在说什么
I don't know what he-- what he's talking about.
我对天发誓
I swear to God.
好  我们会帮你的
All right, we will help you.
我们会帮你的  但你得先放她走
We will help you, but you've gotta let her go first.
你要她没用
You don't need her.
来  把她交给我  来
Come on, give her to me. Come on.
把她交给我
Give her to me.
反正我也死定了
I'm dead anyway.
不要
No!
没事了  没事了
It's okay, it's okay.
他一直在说什么
He kept on saying,
他们要回来找我了
"They're coming back for me.
他们要清理门户了
They're tying up loose ends."
我们得先找医生给她看看
We need to get her checked out.
好
Okay.
找个警员陪着她
I want a uniform with her at all times.
医生那边一检查完
And as soon as she's medically cleared,
马上把她带回警署
I want her back at the barn.
明白
You got it.
我妹妹跟她的搭档也遇到过这种事
My sister and her partner went through this.
她们接到电话出外勤
Guy blew his brains out
结果那个人在她们面前开枪自尽了
in front of them on a routine call.
加比没事  但是夏伊受打击很大
Gabby was fine, but it hit Shay pretty hard.
不要不敢跟别人倾诉
Don't be afraid to talk to somebody, anybody.
如果感觉不好的话  尽管找我
Me-- if it sneaks up on you.
-谢谢  -不用客气
- Thanks. - Yeah, appreciate it.
佩格阿姨来了
Aunt Peg's here,
妈妈想跟她一起打牌
and mom and her are trying to play cards.
好  我还有十分钟就行了
All right, ten more minutes.
根据你跟她签署的协议
Well, according to the agreement you signed with her,
你4点钟就不能发出噪音了
noise cutoff time is 4:00.
给我看看
Let me see that.
我不记得签过啊
I don't remember signing anything.
我跟你母亲的事都没问题了
You know, your mother and I got it all worked out.
不用你来做和事佬
There's no need for you to place peacemaker.
如果你这么想离开她
If you want to get away from her so bad,
为什么不另找房子住呢
why don't you just get an apartment?
我住车库不是想远离你母亲
I don't live in the garage to be away from your mother.
而是想离你近点
I live here to be close to you.
爸  你真好
Dad, that's sweet.
是啊  好
Yeah. Sweet.
明天是父女舞会哦
Father/daughter dance tomorrow.
记得帮我挑一套西服
Got my suit picked out.
你要去吗
You wanna go?
当然
Of course!
好  你先稍等
Yeah, I'm gonna put you on hold.
-伯吉斯  阿特沃特  -怎么了
- Burgess, Atwater. - Hmm?
西弗农公园那边有位女士
A lady over on West Vernon Park
后院一直堆着各种东西
has been letting stuff pile up in her backyard,
然后她的狗屁邻居打电话找了治安官
and the buttinski neighbors called the sheriff, apparently,
说让她30天之内清理干净
gave her 30 days to clean it up.
我猜那个老家伙应该没清理
And I guess the old lady hasn't done anything,
所以你们过去
so head over there,
如果她真的没动的话  就把她抓进来
and if she hasn't made any progress, lock her ass up.
就因为她懒就把人家关起来吗
Lock her up for being a slob?
如果哪天你说了算的话  伯吉斯
You know, when you're queen for a day, Burgess,
那你可以做你的好人
you can keep all the happy laws
啥也不用管
and get rid of all the mean ones.
在此之前  滚去干活  好吗
But until then move your buns, okay?
我们会给你带东西回来的  警长
We'll bring something back for you, Sarge.
也许她在地上为你留了
Maybe she's got an old box of personality
一箱子人品呢
laying around there for you.
奥林斯基  你女儿学校的来电在四号线
Olinsky, your daughter's school's on line four.
迪恩·马斯特斯二十几岁时是个自傲的艺术家
Dean Masters was a hotshot artist in his 20s,
没有工作  染上了毒瘾
work dried up, picked up a drug habit.
他不仅有买卖赃物的嫌疑
He's suspected of not only being a fence
还有仿作名画的嫌疑
but also forging paintings.
那他是怎么犯到情报部门头上的呢
What was that thing intelligence had him on?
一幅克里姆的画被盗了  再也没出现过
Stolen Klimt. Never resurfaced.
克里姆是个什么
What the hell is a Klimt?
-一个艺术家  -名字叫克里姆吗
- An artist. - Named Klimt?
-是的  -这名字真搞笑  对吧
- Yeah. - That's a funny name, right?
还是说只有我一个人觉得好笑
Or am I alone on this?
克里姆  大声读出来
Klimt. Say it out loud.
确实有点好笑  是的
It's kinda funny, yeah.
所以马斯特斯说的什么
So this whole "they're gonna kill me" thing
"他们要杀我"的事
that Masters was going on about
极有可能与被盗的画作有关
was either about the stolen painting or something else.
也有可能他只是磕嗨了胡说八道而已
Or he was just tripping and talking nonsense.
你看到他的瞳孔了吗  肯定是嗑得神志不清了
I mean, did you see his pupils? He was gakked out of his mind.
所以我们掌握的这个嫌疑人
We got a known suspect,
因为想逃避责任所以自杀了
took his own life rather than face something heavy-duty.
我们继续追查这个案子
We pursue the case.
她会照顾你的
She'll take care of you.
琳德赛  你过来处理一下
Lindsay, will you take this?
你感觉怎样
How you feeling?
糟糕透顶
Like hell.
是啊
Yeah.
过来喝杯咖啡吧
Let's get a cup of coffee.
我得去一下莱克西的学校
I gotta run to Lexi's school in a bit.
-有什么事吗  -没事
- Everything all right? - Yeah, it's fine.
好  去吧
Okay, cool.
我应该谢谢你昨晚救了我
I guess I should thank you for last night.
他选择爆了自己的头  而不是你的
Well, he chose his head instead of yours.
我们都很走运
We all got lucky.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事的
It's okay.
你有多了解迪恩·马斯特斯
How well did you know Dean Masters?
我昨晚才认识的他
I just met him last night.
这不过是我们第三次做  做那种事
It was only the third time I've ever...done that.
我是一个职业美容师
I'm a licensed esthetician.
直到一周前我都在一个美容沙龙工作
I worked at a salon up till about a week ago.
但我付不起房租
I wasn't making rent.
也许这正说明了你不适合那种生活吧
Maybe this is a sign that that life's not for you, huh?
是的
Yeah.
你知道为什么迪恩觉得你陷害他吗
Do you know why Dean thought you were trying to set him up?
我不知道
I don't know.
我对天发誓  我到那儿的时候
I swear to God, I got there,
他就已经很生气了
and--and he was pissed
因为我不是他要的那个女孩
because I wasn't the girl he asked for and--
他想要的是谁
Who was he expecting?
娜迪亚
Nadia.
女士
Ma'am?
你好
Hello.
我是伯吉斯警官  他是阿特沃特警官
I'm officer Burgess. This is officer Atwater.
你们好
Hello.
埃文斯太太  您超过30天的时限了
Ms. Evans, you've exceeded the 30 days--
我正在打扫  抱歉
I'm trying. I'm sorry.
我在努力整理  但就是没法...
I'm trying, but I just can't seem to...
开始
get started.
我们不得不逮捕您了  女士
We're gonna have to place you under arrest, ma'am.
请您能转身
If you could turn around for me.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我  我需要和我同伴谈谈
I just--I need to talk to my partner.
很快的  女士
Real quick, ma'am.
我不会把这个女士铐起来的
I'm not locking this lady up.
你不知道因果报应这回事吗
You wanna talk about some bad karma?
我宁愿遭报应也不想惹普拉特  知道吗
Well, I'd rather piss her off than Platt, feel me?
等等
Wait.
女士  您能帮我个忙吗
Ma'am, would you do me a favor?
您能把您身后那个咖啡罐给我吗
Would you grab that coffee can behind you?
那一个  对的
That one. There you go.
把那个香蕉皮
Now take that banana peel--
或者不管那是什么  捡起来
or whatever it is.
对对对
Yep, yep, yep.
好的  把它丢到咖啡罐里
Okay, now drop it in the coffee can.
暂时可以了
Good enough for us.
祝您愉快  女士
Have a good day, ma'am,
请您一定要把房子打扫干净
and please do get your house cleaned up,
否则您一定会被其他的警员逮捕的
or indeed you will be arrested by other officers.
搞定啦
Just like that.
这一块是亚当·马苏尔的地盘
Guy who runs this place is Adam Mazur.
-我是在缉捕队时知道他的  -好的
- I know him from vice. - Right.
他们叫他地鼠皮条男
Called him the whac-a-mole pimp.
我们搞定他  然后一个星期后
We'd beat him down, and he'd pop up somewhere else
他又会在另一个地方建个窝
a week later with a new stable.
-出发  -好的
- Let's go. - All right.
你们是会员吗
Membership, guys?
是啊  看这里
Yeah. Right here.
敢按报警器  我就打断你的手
If you press an alarm, I will break your hand.
趴墙上  马上去  转身
Get up against the wall. Now. Turn around.
芝加哥警署  大家不要惊慌
Chicago PD. Everybody stay calm.
把手伸出来  谢谢
Put your hands where I can see 'em, please.
把手放在我看得见的地方
Put your hands where I can see 'em.
你好啊  马苏尔
How you doing, Mazur?
你手下有叫娜迪亚的姑娘吗
Got a girl named Nadia?
从来没听过她
Never heard of her.
-她在八号房间  -谢谢
- She's in room eight. - Thank you, thank you.
有人在吗
Knock, knock.
我这是在接受合法按摩
I was getting a legitimate massage.
就算你是吧  出去  快点
I'll bet you were. Get out there, come on!
快走
Go!
你是娜迪亚吗
Are you Nadia?
别对我开枪  求你了
Please don't shoot me.
我不会对你开枪的  没事的
I'm not gonna shoot you. Everything's gonna be fine.
-好吗  -好的
- All right? - Okay.
-跟我走  -好的
- Just come with me. - Okay.
你会没事的
You'll be all right.
-谢谢你  -好的
- Thank you. - Yeah.
-给你  -谢谢
- Here. - Thanks.
我觉得肯定肿了
I think they're swollen.
说真的  兄弟
Seriously, dude.
我相信你
I'll take your word for it.
娜迪亚在罗斯福大街
Uniforms picked up Nadia
想买毒品的时候被抓住了
trying to score over on Roosevelt.
他们把她带回来了
They're bringing her in.
-你还好吗  -不好
- You all right? - No.
我就是问问而已
Just checking.
牺牲下自己娱乐了大家  真棒啊
Yeah, I'm glad we're all having fun with this.
安东尼奥  我和温迪还想要孩子呢
Antonio, Wendy and I wanna have kids.
如果我不行了的话
If I'm sterile...
我要把那妞的脖子拧下来
I'm gonna have that chick's neck.
这都怪你  鲁塞克
This is all on you, Ruzek.
做警察的不能那样放松警惕  绝对不行
You can't let your guard down like that, ever.
说得好
Good talk.
我们在莱克西的储物柜里发现了这些
We found these in Lexi's locker.
我知道您是干什么的
I know what you do for a living,
所以我就让您来处理这件事吧
so I'm going to let you handle it.
但是  我们这里是零容忍政策
But... we have a zero tolerance policy.
她要自动停学  一周
It's an automatic suspension. One week.
我该怎么跟你妈妈说
What am I going to say to your mother?
我可以躲在车库里  帮你干活
I'll hide in the garage. Works for you.
你什么时候开始抽大麻的
When did you start smoking pot?
-那不是我的  老爸  -那是谁的
- They weren't mine, dad. - Then whose were they?
不知道  我捡的
No one's. I found them.
是吗  是不是你那个高三男朋友的吗
Oh? Is it that senior with the stupid name
名字很白痴的那个
that you've been seeing?
不是的
No.
那好吧  在家见
All right, see you at home.
老爸  只是大麻  别太小题大做了
Dad, they're just joints. Please don't go crazy.
我知道
It's okay.
跟我说说迪恩·马斯特斯吧
So what can you tell me about Dean Masters?
不熟  我就跟他约过一次
Didn't really know him. I went on one date with the guy.
你确定吗  我听说你是他的最爱呢
You sure about that? I heard you were his favorite.
我经常听人这么说
Yeah, I get that a lot.
肯定的
I bet.
好了  你在哪儿长大的
All right, so where'd you grow up?
哪一个社区
What neighborhood?
森林湖城  我是返校节皇后
Lake Forest. I was homecoming queen,
迈克尔·乔丹就住隔壁
and Michael Jordan was our neighbor.
是嘛  我也在那儿长大  我还是优秀毕业生呢
Really? You know, I grew up there too. I was the valedictorian.
说实话  你几岁了
Seriously, how old are you?
你知道我可以在两分钟内就查出来
You know I can find out in two minutes.
差一个月满十八
18 in a month.
我用的是假身份证  所以别找他们麻烦
But I used a fake I.D., so don't hassle 'em.
我需要那份工作
I need the work.
所以迪恩提过他和谁有过节吗
So Dean mention having any problems with anybody?
没有
Nope.
你本来想买什么毒品  海洛因吗
What were you trying to score, heroin?
听着  我可以给你弄点
Look... I can get you a fix.
我向你保证
You have my word on that.
但你得先开口交待
But I need some information first.
迪恩为什么要自杀  他有仇家吗
Why would Dean eat a bullet? He had enemies?
没有  正好相反
No. The opposite.
迪恩很讲义气
Dean was the sharing type.
他是谁
Give me a name.
圣诞老人
Santa.
一个叫圣诞老人的人吗
Guy named Santa?
不  不  这是我记住他的方法
No, no. That's how I remembered it.
诺  尔
"No-el."
诺尔  诺尔·哈瑞斯
Noel. Noel Harris.
对  他买的海洛因
Yeah, he brought the skag.
他在波尔克有家卡片店还是什么的
He owns some sort of card shop or some deal over on Polk.
我不清楚  他这人到处跑
I don't know. He was rambling.
好了  咱们走吧
Okay. Let's go.
你这是干什么
Hey, what're you doing?
就在这待一会儿吧
Just for a little while.
你最好给我回来  贱人  回来
You better come back here, bitch! I mean it!
一堆的烦死人的邻居抱怨
Multiple pain-in-the-ass neighbors have complained
你们两个蠢蛋屁事都没干
that you two dolts didn't do a damn thing.
埃文斯女士很有诚意地...
Ms. Evans was making a good-faith effort to--
你这是在帮她出头吗  伯吉斯
What are you, on the stand now, Burgess?
还有诚意
A good-faith effort?
她把你的胆都放到杂物箱里吗  阿特沃特
Does she keep your balls in the glove box, Atwater?
据我所知没有
Not that I know of.
那为什么什么都是她说了算
Then why is she calling the shots all the time?
你们再去一趟
You go back there,
如果那个疯子的清扫工作还没有进展
and if that nutcase hasn't made a serious dent in the clean-up,
你就把她铐给我回来
you slap some bracelets on her and you bring her in...
要不然我就把你们安排去指挥交通
or I will park you both on crossing guard duty,
也许你们就这点本事了
which is maybe where you belong,
因为我最不耐烦软蛋警察
'cause I got no patience for soft cops.
现在马上去
Now get outta here.
-对不起  -这次我去跟那位女士交涉
- Sorry. - I'll deal with this lady now.
当然  我理解
Of course. I understand.
我会处理好的
I'll take care of it.
是佩里局长打来的
That was Commander Perry.
你得把这件事给了结了
You gotta end this.
-了结什么事  -罗迪杰一家的事啊
- End what? - The Rodiger family.
他们先是申了个遏制令
First a restraining order.
现在都已经对你正式提起诉讼了
Now they've filed a formal complaint against you with the city.
你不知道这件事的来龙去脉
You don't know the whole story.
其实我知道
I do, actually.
警署可不想你的名字出现在报纸上
This unit does not need your name and face in the papers
标题写什么《复仇警察》
as some "Vendetta cop."
让凶案组去查吧
Just let homicide do their job.
可是他们不干活啊
They're not, though.
然后呢  每次走过朗尼·罗迪杰的家
And what, the family's just gonna have to
家里人都要忍气吞声吗
eat it every time they walk by Lonnie Rodiger's house?
这世界本就不公平  你才知道这道理吗
The world isn't fair. You just learning this?
你有当好警察的潜力  霍斯特德
You got potential to be great police, Halstead.
放下这事吧
So drop it.
有人吗
Hello?
哈里斯先生  芝加哥警署
Mr. Harris? Chicago police.
有人吗
Hello?
诺尔·哈瑞斯
Noel Harris!
看看这个
Look at this.
这人到底是卖卡片还是热裤
This guy selling cards or Daisy Dukes?
《正义前锋》里的Daisy Dukes
穿短到不能再短的热裤
我们来晚了
We're too late.
在垃圾里找到一堆这个
Found a bunch of this in the trash.
这是什么
What's that?
你知道为什么
You know how you can run money
钱放洗衣机里洗过还不会破吗
through the washer and it doesn't rip up?
那是因为钱不是纸做的
That's 'cause it's not made out of paper.
是布  和蓝牛仔裤同一种布料
It's made out of fabric. Same stuff in blue jeans.
看见了吗  料子很好  这个人很在行
See? Perfect texture. This guy was good.
你去让所有人都到马斯特斯的家里
I want you to get everybody over to Masters' house.
里里外外都搜一遍
I want that place searched inside out.
知道了  这就去安排
Yeah, you got it.
卧室没问题
Bedrooms are clear.
我们漏掉了一块地方
We're missing 20 square feet.
就在这里
Right there.
是这里吗
You got it?
找到了
Bingo.
看吧  我就说这个人有两下子
See, I mean, that is some serious talent, man.
-这个人是个失败的艺术家吗  -对
- This guy's a failed artist? - Yep.
人们本行如果混不下去
It's funny the things people end up doing
真是花样百出啊
when they can't do what they really want, huh?
这是乔·希尔探员
This is Agent Joe Hill.
特勤局  芝加哥分局的
Secret service, Chicago field office.
我们是老相识了
We go back a ways.
你的耳机和墨镜呢
Where's your earpiece and your sunglasses?
只有奥巴马来的时候才会用到
That's only when Obama's in town.
这意味着我们要把案子移交出去吗
Does this mean we're handing over the case?
不是  按照规定来说我不能插手
No. Technically I can't get involved
除非真的出现假币
unless there's actual counterfeit currency found,
但是汉克觉得我能帮上忙
But Hank just thought I could help.
我以为如今造假币的都使用高端打印机了
I thought counterfeiters were using high-end printers nowadays.
现在数码技术可以打印出乱真的五块和十块
There's digital tech that'll print a pretty good 5 or 10,
然后在沃尔格林[美国最大连锁药店]买东西花光
then you pass it off at Walgreens buying dollar items.
我们管那个叫"婴儿洗钱"
That's what we call "Baby laundering."
而用模板  这可是个老派的方法
Using plates-- this is old-school.
需要真功夫
Takes some real work.
一共有三步
There's three steps.
雕版  钞纸和印刷机
The plates, the paper, and the printer.
猜猜我们现在该找谁
Guess who we're looking for now.
踢鲁塞克蛋蛋的那个妓女
The hooker that kicked Ruzek in the nuts.
她是怎么说自己和迪恩·马斯特斯的关系的
How'd she characterize her interaction with Dean Masters?
只去过他家一次
Went to his place once.
过去两周他们俩之间有45条短信来往
45 text messages between him and her over the last two weeks.
-你说了会帮我弄粉来的  -我会的
- You said you'd hook me up. - And I will.
你一定要帮帮我  一定要...
You gotta help me. You gotta...
好了  坐下吧
Okay, come on.
坐下吧
Come on.
娜迪亚  看着我
Nadia. Hey. Focus.
你为什么要骗我
Why'd you lie to me?
我招出了诺尔  还不够吗
I gave you Noel! Isn't that enough?
什么时候够了我会告诉你的
I'll tell you when it's enough.
你还想不这么百爪挠心吗
Do you want to get well? Huh?
我可以给你弄来你要的东西
I can get you the fix that you need,
但我要你告诉我到底是怎么回事
but I need you to tell me what's going on.
他们说会杀了我的
They said they'd kill me.
谁说的
Who?
前几晚我有次在迪恩家
I was at Dean's a few nights ago.
那是我最后一次看到他
It was the last time I saw him.
他出去帮我们买毒品
He went out to score for us.
我去屋外抽了根烟
I went out front to have a smoke
因为他不喜欢别人在他家里抽
'cause he didn't like it in the house.
一群带着枪的男人走进来
A group of guys with guns walked up.
有个人拿走了他的手机  照了张我的照片
One of 'em took out his cell phone and took a picture of me,
说如果我敢开口  就会找到我杀了我
said if I said anything he'd find me and kill me.
好吧  他长什么样
Okay. What did he look like?
年轻黑人  穿着帽衫牛仔裤
Young. Black. Jeans, hoodies.
我特别害怕  就赶快离开了
I was so scared I just...left.
但我看到他们进了一辆面包车
But I saw them get into this delivery van...
车上画着耶稣鱼的标志
with a Jesus fish painted on it.
基督教代表符号
希腊语"鱼"写做"Ichthys"
什么
What?
清醒点
Hey!
你是在耍我吗
Is this you tripping?
不  我指天发誓
No. I swear to God.
车背后有很大一幅耶稣鱼的图
There was a big Jesus fish painted on the back of the truck.
好吧
Okay.
穿上
Come on.
冷吗  你做得很好
You cold? You did good.
-给你  -现在能去买粉了吗
- Here. - Now can we go score?
快了
Soon.
我发誓  如果你敢骗我的话
I swear to God, if you're lying to me,
-我绝对...  -你绝对怎么样
- I'm gonna-- - You're gonna what?
你知道我现在能给你多少项指控吗
Do you have any idea how many charges I could drop on you right now?
我说了我会照顾你  我就肯定会
I told you I would take care of you and I will.
所以我需要你冷静点  耐心等待
So I need you to take it down a notch and wait.
来吧
Come on.
警方监控里找到了符合描述的面包车
Okay, PODS found a match to the delivery van
车后有张耶稣鱼的图案
with the Jesus fish on the back.
你们知道吗  这个标志实际上叫做"伊克塞斯"
You know, the symbol's actually called an Ichthys--
-行了吉恩  -好吧
- Jin? - Fine.
你们想继续叫"耶稣鱼"就叫吧
You wanna keep calling it a "Jesus fish," knock yourself out.
还发现了别的东西
Also found something else.
-帐幕吗  -对
- Tabernacle? - Yeah.
这辆车注册在"神之帐幕"名下
This van's registered to the Tabernacle of Divinity.
是座位于63街和加州大街路口的沿街教堂
It's a storefront church on 63rd and Cal.
他们用这种车给老年人送饭
They use it to deliver meals to the elderly.
麦克牧师在那里  原来是混帮派的
That's Pastor Mike's place. An ex-GD.
几年前应该坐过牢的
Supposedly underwent a jailhouse conversion a few years back.
我猜还是没坐够啊
Guess it didn't take.
好的  我去让娜迪亚
All right. I'll show Nadia a lineup
认认这人和他同伙
of this guy and his associates.
如果她认出来谁  我就去弄搜查令
If she picks anybody out, I'll get a warrant.
-谢两位了  -别客气
- Thanks, gents. - No problem.
-布雷登  -是我
- Brayden. - Yeah.
埃尔文·奥林斯基  莱克西的父亲
Alvin Olinsky. Lexi's dad.
您好  先生
Yeah. Hey...sir.
我们从来没正式见过
We never actually met...
因为你每次来接我女儿的时候
because every time you come over to pick up my daughter
都只是坐在车里
you've only stayed out in the car.
是的  是我不好
Yeah, that's my bad.
你看什么看
What the hell are you looking at?
不用管她
Hey, don't mind her.
我们在莱克西的储物柜
Do you know anything about the joints
里找到的大麻  你知情吗
that were found in Lexi's locker?
不  先生
No, sir.
把手机给我
Let me have your phone.
今天她没给你发短信吗
So, uh... no texts from her today?
还是你都删掉了
Or did you just erase them all?
我们还没有...
Uh, we haven't...
说过话  或者发短信  所以...
talked, you know, or texted, so...
来  过来
Come here. Come on.
我是被逮捕了吗
Yo, am I under arrest?
你该被逮捕吗
Well, should you be?
-不  我只是问一下  -坐下
- No, I was just asking. - Sit.
神之帐幕
警察  所有人都趴下
Police! Everybody get on the ground!
趴在地上
Get on the ground!
双手抱着头
Put your hands behind your head!
趴墙上
On the wall!
给我跪下  拿走枪
Down on your knees! Gun!
拿走枪
Gun!
说什么  闭嘴  趴下
What? Shut up! Get down!
别看我  手举起来
Don't look at me, man. Keep your hands up!
-举高点  -转过去
- Put 'em up higher! - Turn around!
把手放背后  以为我在开玩笑吗
Put your hands back! Think I'm kidding you?
这只也给我  手心朝外
Gimme this one. Palm to the sky.
神的战士吗  麦克
God's soldier, huh, Mike?
这些钱是他赐给你的吗
He bless you with all this cash?
伙计  那些只是大家捐赠的福利送餐的钱
Man, those are just donations for our Meals on Wheels.
听好  所有人都闭嘴  什么都别说
Hey, keep y'all mouths shut! Don't say nothing!
没有雕版  没有钞纸
No plates. No paper.
没有任何印刷操作的迹象
No sign of any printing operation.
麦克牧师真的有那个本事做伪钞吗
We really think Pastor Mike has the skills for counterfeiting?
莱克西发给你短信  问你在哪里
I got a text from Lexi asking where you are.
回复她  "我在忙呢  怎么了"
Text her back. "I'm busy, what's up?"
读出来
Read it.
"我觉得我爸知道我帮你藏大麻了"
"I think my dad knows I was holding for you."
真的很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
我在申请上大学
My applications went out for college,
档案里不能被记上这笔  知道吗
and I couldn't have those joints on my record, you know?
站起来
Stand up.
别让我再看见你
I don't ever want to see you again.
好的  先生
You won't, sir.
很好  从现在开始
Yeah. Starting now.
滚吧
Go.
-夫人  -我在打扫了
- Ma'am? - I've been cleaning.
打扫了卧室  打扫了里面房间
In my bedroom, in the back.
我们需要看一下
We'll need to see it.
我没有骗你
I promise you.
夫人  我们需要看下您的进展
Ma'am, we need to see progress,
否则我们就得逮捕您
or we're going to have to place you under arrest.
好吧
Okay.
你们看  都清理到这里了
Look, see? It's all here.
我一直在打扫清理呢
I've been working on it.
请离开吧
Now please... leave.
-听见了吗  -什么
- Did you hear that? - No. What?
后面传来的
It's back there.
你不能下去  你没有授权
Do not go down there! You're not allowed!
-出去  -里面有什么
- No. Get out! - What's in there?
没什么  你得走了
Nothing. You need to leave.
你们没权在这里
You have no right to be in here.
我们有  打开它
Yeah, we do. Open it.
别
No!
-快闪开  -女士
- No, get away from there! - Ma'am!
-不  -女士
- No! - Ma'am!
走开  不  不
Get away! No! No!
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
我的老天
Oh, my God.
没事了
Hey, it's okay.
妈妈说不能和陌生人说话
Mama said no strangers.
没错  可是现在没关系  你安全了
Okay, but it's all right now. You're safe.
过来
Come here.
没事了
It's okay. Yeah.
没事了  没事了
It's okay, it's okay.
没事了
It's okay.
我们向你道歉  麦克牧师
We owe you an apology, pastor Mike.
继续说
That's a start.
我们以前怀疑你是一起
I mean, here we were thinking you're the brains
假币案的幕后主使
behind a counterfeit ring.
可你只是太单纯
But really you're a small-time charlie
单纯到都不知道自己被耍了
Who's too dumb to know you've been played.
不对  当前的苦痛
Naw. "The sufferings of this present time
不可与神的光辉相提并论
are not worth comparing to the glories of God."
罗马人的谚语
That's Romans.
小伎俩而已
That's some kind of trick.
你的人除掉了诺尔·哈瑞斯
Your crew took out Noel Harris.
迪恩·马斯特斯知道在你的名单上
Dean Masters knew he was on your list.
他吓坏了  所以干脆自杀了
He freaks out, kills himself first.
问题是  你拿到的薪水是假钱
And the problem is... you got paid in funny money.
到底是谁雇了你
Why don't you tell us who hired you
对哈瑞斯下手
for the hit on Harris.
我可以跟州检察官说说
I'll talk to the state's attorney,
看看能不能判你个20年  不终身监禁
see about you getting 20 years instead of life.
好吧
All right.
雇麦克牧师的是这个人
Pastor Mike was contracted by this man...
格林·沃德
Glen Ward.
沃德因制假钞在莱文沃斯
Now, Ward has done federal time in Leavenworth
服过刑
for counterfeiting.
但是沃德和他手下印刷的人
But how Ward and his printing crew
是怎么跟迪安·马斯特斯和诺尔·哈瑞斯
hooked up with Dean Masters and Noel Harris
勾搭在一起的  他们两个
is anybody's guess, and why the two of them
又为什么现在都死了呢
are both dead now, who knows?
麦克牧师没说过沃德为什么想让他们死吗
Pastor Mike didn't say why Ward wanted them dead?
-他没问  -有很多可能性
- He didn't ask. - It could be any reason.
分赃不均
Somebody wanted a bigger cut,
威胁要告发同伙  上了人家的女人之类
threatened to snitch, banged somebody's girlfriend.
都有可能
Any one of those scenarios.
沃德其中一个化名叫做德尼·狄德罗
One of Ward's aliases is Denis Diderot.
不仅是个做假钞的  还挺热爱法国文学
A counterfeiter and a fan of French literature.
等不及要见见他了
Can't wait to meet him.
警长
Hey, Sarge.
吉恩刚刚拿名字
Jin just did a name check
核对了一遍新的商业地产租约
against new leases on commercial property rentals.
他收到风声
He got a hit.
提前关闭了西塞罗市的化工建筑
Foreclosed chemical building on Cicero.
好吧  如果大家都不反对加班的话
All right, unless anyone's opposed to overtime,
我们就去把他揪出来吧
let's go find our printer.
这个时候我该告诉你
This is the part where I'm supposed to tell you
特勤处要接管这个案子了
secret service is taking over the case.
不不不  我们说好了的
No, no, no. We had a deal.
犯人归我  假钞归你
I get the bad guys. You get the counterfeit money.
这就是我一直等到早上的原因
That's why I'm waiting until morning to do it.
你为什么那么做
Why did you do that?
莱克西
Lexi...
他就是个人渣
He's a dirtbag.
我的朋友们都知道你威胁他了
Now all my friends know that you threatened him
就因为几包大麻
over a couple of joints?
事情不是这样  莱克西
That's not what this is about, Lexi,
不止是因为几包大麻  那个无所谓
about a couple of joints. It doesn't matter.
让他载你一程什么的无所谓
This guy was perfectly happy to let you take the ride.
但他还不是个男人  他永远不可能成熟
He's not a man. He never will be.
他配不上你
And he doesn't deserve you.
莱克西
Lexi.
看看我发现谁在楼梯上面闲逛
Look who I found loitering at the top of the stairs.
一切都还好吗
Is everything all right?
一切都好  老爸
Yeah. Yeah, it's all good, pop.
怎么了
What's up?
你就是在这里向手下的人发号施令的  是吗
So this is where you hand down commands to your crew, huh?
没错  我正要走呢
This is it. 'Bout to roll out, actually.
不错  我想和你聊聊
Cool. Hey, uh, actually wanna talk to you
一会儿就好
about something real quick, pop.
-好  -我有个机会...
- Uh-huh. - So I got a chance...
有这么一个入股的机会
I got a chance to get in on the ground floor
是一个朋友的生意
of a business that my buddy's putting together.
-哦  -我是说  这生意
- Mm-hmm. - I mean, there is no ceiling
利润非常可观
on how profitable this could get.
-什么生意  -回收
- What is it? - Recycling
然后翻新手机
and refurbishing cell phones.
他想出了一个崭新的商业模式
My buddy's got a whole new business model, though.
切入点也和以往类似的公司不同
He's coming at it from a whole new angle.
我感觉这笔投资有盼头
I feel like this could really set me up, pop.
-我觉得有戏  -要多少钱
- I feel it could be a good thing. - How much?
一万块  但是一个月就能收回来
10 grand. But I can get it back to you in a month.
-最多两个月  -你凭什么认为
- Two months, max. - What makes you think
我手头会有一万块现金
I got 10 grand laying around?
我知道你有副业收入
I know you got side income.
这话什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我不是小孩子了  爸爸
I'm not a kid anymore, dad.
我知道你做事有你的一套
I know you do things your way.
我在里面的时候甚至听到过一些
I even heard things when I was inside
你收保护费的事
about you charging street taxes?
你听错了
You heard wrong.
好吧  那我妈妈的保险费呢
All right. Then what about mom's life insurance?
我知道银行里还有一部分钱
I know you still got some of that in the bank.
我不能用一点吗
Aren't I entitled to a piece of that?
贾斯汀  那些钱大部分都用做你的律师费了
Justin, most of that was used for your legal fees.
我跟你说吧
Look, I'll tell you what.
你去芝加哥交管局干六个月...
You put six months under your vest at CTA--
我等不了  我现在就要
I need the money now, not six months from now.
六个月后生意都没戏了
In six months, the deal is dead.
芝加哥交管局的安迪·莫里西
Andy Morrissey at CTA.
在等你的回电
He's expecting your call.
知道了
Copy that.
四年前他在南达科他州被列为
He was listed as a missing person in South Dakota
失踪人员
four years ago.
在那之后他们就搬过来了
They moved here right after that.
孩子的爸爸已经不在世了
Dad's out of the picture. Fell through the cracks.
你还好吗
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
前面很安静
It's quiet out front.
看来沃德准备逃了
Looks like Ward's ready to roll.
能监视到里面的情形吗
We got eyes in there yet?
还不行  就快好了  再等等
No. Almost there. Stand by.
好了  能看到了  造假老窝
All right, we're up. Counterfeit central.
-好  转下镜头  -好的
- All right, give 'er a spin. - All right.
有两个人
There's two.
三个  四个人
Three, and...four.
-有武器吗  -无法判断
- Any artillery? - I can't tell.
闯进去吧
We're going in.
-芝加哥警局  -小心  有条子
- Chicago PD! - Watch out--the police!
不准动
Halt!
-我去对付沃德  -我对付这个
- I got Ward! - I got this one!
-不准动  不准动  -举起手来
- Don't move! Don't move! - Drop it!
不许起来
Stay down!
枪放在仪表盘上  举起手来  快
Gun on the dash. Hands on your head! Now!
G5021  紧急情况
George 5021 emergency.
警察和对方都开枪了
Shots fired by the police and at the police.
派一辆救护车到13街南的1356号
Roll an ambo to 1356 south 13th street.
通知迪克斯和取证室
Notify the Dicks and crime lab.
现场有便衣警察
Plainclothes officers at the scene.
需不需要件T恤  大伙计
Can I get you a T-shirt, big fella?
你还好吗  要是真的就好了
You good? Too bad it ain't real.
琳德赛  拍张照片给我做唱片封面
Lindsay, get a picture of me for my album cover.
真是个白痴
You're an idiot.
打给希尔探员  说我们找到了造假老窝
Call Agent Hill, tell him we found the mother lode.
呵呵  力气我们出
Yeah, we do all the work,
风头却是特勤处的
secret service comes in, takes the credit.
你想让你的脸
You want your face
出现在报纸头条上吗
on the front page of the paper?
博伊特
Voight.
伯吉斯  阿特沃特
Burgess, Atwater!
之前的案子办得不错
Nice police work on that hoarder deal.
不过是歪打正着
We kinda just stumbled into that.
发现了青霉素的呆子
The egghead who discovered penicillin
也不过是歪打正着
just stumbled into it too.
结果最重要
A win's a win.
谢谢警长
Thanks, Sarge.
开心点
Hey, you cheer up.
从普拉特那儿得到赞扬可不简单
It's no small thing getting a compliment from Platt.
我头一次听到赞扬会如坐针毡
I was in such a hurry to leave that first time.
要是我们没找到他呢
What if we never found him?
没事了  那个孩子也会没事的
It worked out. And the kid's gonna be okay.
有时候我觉得自己太热心肠  不适合当警察
Sometimes...I think I'm too nice to be a cop.
你心肠很好
You got a big heart, all right?
这没什么不好
Don't apologize for that.
你认识那家人吗
You knew the family?
他是我上中学时前女友的弟弟
He's the younger brother of a girl I dated in high school.
他的父母  丹尼和盖尔
And his parents, Danny and Gail,
也都参加了我的毕业典礼
they came to my graduation from academy.
本本该过生日的日子我还能见到他们
I still see 'em on what would be Ben's birthday.
我和我的搭档最早到的犯罪现场
Me and my partner were first on the scene.
我看到一只鞋
And...I see a shoe,
然后我把芦苇拨开
and then I push the reeds back...
发现了他
and there he is.
我清楚地记得他的惨状
I can still see his face.
我记得他爸为他提供了不在场证明
I remember his dad alibied him out.
但是他们没抓到朗尼的把柄  对吗
But they never had anything on Lonnie, nothing?
不是
No.
在发现本的前一周  警察发现他
They caught him jerking it outside an elementary school
在小学外当众打飞机
a week prior to finding Ben.
他的电脑里满是恋童黄片
They found kiddie porn on his computer...
还有他给本拍的私密照片
and secret pictures that he'd taken of Ben.
-你一定是在开玩笑  -不
- You gotta be kidding me. - Uh-uh.
我们都清楚是朗尼干的
We all knew Lonnie did it.
但是  他爸爸撒谎了  还请了个好律师
But, you know, his dad lied, and they got a good lawyer.
我说你要当心
Hey... be careful.
听到了吗
Hear me?
父女舞会就在今晚  但是
Father/daughter dance is tonight, but...
我现在被停学了
I'm suspended.
你要穿那件衣服吗
Are you wearing that?
我不想让你出去找公寓住
I don't want you to get an apartment.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
他和他的同伴在米勒酒吧
Him and his buddy got a little rowdy
大闹了一场
over at Miller's pub.
-爸  听我  -闭嘴
- Pop, liste-- - Shut up.
谢谢你没把这事记录在案  史蒂夫
Appreciate you not booking him, Steve.
省的写文件了
Saves us the paperwork.
-被打的孩子怎么样了  -跟他差不多
- How's the kid he fought? - Mm, 'bout the same.
对方会不会提起正式诉讼
Not looking to press charges down the line?
需要帮忙的话尽管跟我说
Listen, you need anything, you let me know.
保重
Be safe.
走吧
Walk.
那个跟你在一起的家伙是谁
Who's this buddy you were with?
你不认识他
You don't know him.
一群墨西哥佬嘴上不老实
Bunch of wannabe cholos were talking smack,
就跟酒吧是他们开的似的
acting like they run the place.
他们不尊重我们  爸
They were disrespecting us, pop.
你知道我在那里面经历了什么吗
Do you have any idea what I went through in there?
-一个警察的儿子在里面  -说完了没
- The son of a cop? - You finished?
我要你好好听我说一次话  行吗
I want you to listen to me for once, dad, okay?
我跟进去之前的我不一样了
I'm not the same kid that I was when I walked in there.
如果你能在一开始就打通关系
Maybe if you would've done your job
早点把我保出来...
and kept me out in the first place--
你想说你现在这样都是我的错
You wanna blame me for what you do?
-听我说  -什么
- You know what? - Hmm.
去你妈的
Screw you.
娜迪亚
Nadia.
到时间了
It's time.
你说真的吗
You telling the truth?
对  跟我来
Yeah, come on.
你真的让我买去毒品吗
You really just gonna let me go score?
我想让你做出抉择
I'm letting you make a choice.
所以我才会在你清醒的时候带你来这儿
That's why I wanted you to do it sober.
因为你还有别的选择
'Cause there is another way.
街对面的戒毒所
That clinic across the street
能够帮助你重新做人
has everything you need to get started.
所以  在你下车之后
So...you're gonna get out,
我会把车开走
I'm gonna drive away,
然后你自己做出选择
and then the choice is yours.
到底是去戒毒所  还是去买毒品
Walk over to the clinic, or walk across the street and buy.
这个决定必须要由你自己做出
This is a decision that you have to make for yourself,
否则我们就是在浪费时间
otherwise we're just wasting our time here.
拿着我的名片
Take my card.
如果你想过上美好的生活
If you want a life better than what you got...
我会尽可能地帮助你
I will help you get to the other side.
我向你保证
That is a promise.